# AISHWARYA PEARALA

 $\bowtie$ 

apearala@gmail.com

C

9496569956

9

Toronto, Ontario M5J2Y7

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

An innovative and resourceful 3D Artist with 4+ years experience in creating and delivering world class 3D models. Self-motivated and a hard working professional accustomed to performing well under pressure and completing all projects within given schedule.

On recently receiving my Canadian PR, I have moved to Canada and now ready to explore interesting opportunities in 3D Art.

## **SKILLS**

- 3D Visualization
- 3D Modeling
- UV unwrapping and Layout
- Texturing
- Lighting
- Rendering
- 2d Traditional Sketching and Digital Art

#### Software's

- Adobe Photoshop
- AutoDesk Maya
- Z-Brush
- Substance Painter
- Blender
- Procreate
- Nomad Sculpt

#### **EDUCATION**

Indira Gandhi National Open University (IGNOU) Hyderabad, INDIA • 2013

Bachelor of Arts: 3D Animation

And Visual Effects

## WEBSITE, PORTFOLIO, PROFILES

- https://aishwaryapearala.blogspot.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/aishwarya-pearala-806358159/
- https://sketchfab.com/aishpearala

### **WORK HISTORY**

Elorce Industries - Senior 3D Artist Hyderabad, INDIA • 11/2020 - 04/2021

- Worked with other artists and programmers to execute projects on time and within budget constraints along with maintaining 100% client satisfaction and technical quality throughout the pipeline
- Worked on government project as Team Lead having 4+ members and successfully delivered 3D model for AR and VR projection.
- Performed key responsibilities such as making "Realistic 3D Models"; UV unwrapping and layout, Texturing, Lighting and Rendering ready for AR and VR projection.
- Few other responsibilities include tracking and assigning work ; reviewing skills and mentoring team members ; performing quality analysis (QA).

# Amazon - Junior 3D Artist Hyderabad, INDIA • 07/2018 - 04/2020

- Responsible for the creation of hard surface 3D assets and texture materials for the AR and VR web-based, real-time applications and photorealistic rendering.
- Used Maya to create 3D models; Substance Painter and Photoshop for texturing and Z-brush for sculpting across multiple projects.

- Maintained high standards for accuracy, aesthetics and productivity across projects.
- Key responsibilities include making end-to-end "Realistic 3D Models"; along with working on UV unwrapping, Texturing, Lighting and Rendering workflows.
- · Worked in a dynamic environment with very tight deadlines.

# Cyient Ltd - Junior Graphic Technician Hyderabad, INDIA • 06/2016 - 06/2018

- Took an active role in analyzing the client requirements and creating realistic 3D landmarks such as building, stadiums and point of interest to TOM-TOM navigation system which is required for AR and VR applications.
- Worked with clients to gather and define requirements, establish scopes and managing project milestones.
- Managed design conceptualization, milestones and customer feedback.
- Obtained multiple employee of the month awards for maintaining and satisfying 100% client requirements.